freebiegroceries.com 2013-06-03

# Freebie Groceries

## Privacy Policy

(Amended as of September 6, 2010)  
PLEASE NOTE: OUR PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES FROM TIME TO TIME. PLEASE CHECK BACK FOR UPDATES

### About this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is intended to describe information that we collect from you and how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures. If you have questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to Contact Us. 

### Application of this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to all websites ("Website(s)" or "Site(s)") owned, operated, and controlled exclusively by Recess LLC ("Recess", "we", "our" or "us"), such as freebiegroceries.com. 

### Links to Third Parties

For your convenience and to improve the usage of the Site, we may insert links to third parties on our Site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to such third party websites. This includes links from partners that may use Recess's logos as part of a co-branding agreement. The sites that such links may direct you to have their own separate privacy policy. Recess is not liable for the content and activities of those sites. Your visits and access to such websites is at your own risk. Please note that third parties' sites may utilize their own cookies with users, collect users' data, and/or solicit users' personal information. 

### Agreement to Terms of Privacy Policy and Terms of Use

All activities in which you may engage on our Site are voluntary. You are not required to provide any personal information to us unless you choose to access features on this Site. If you do not agree with the terms of this policy or other terms of use on this Site, then you should immediately exit this Site and discontinue using the Site. The Terms of Service of this Site are expressly incorporated herein by reference and made a part of this policy. By using the Site, you signify that you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as well as to our Terms of Service. 

### No Use of This Site by Persons Under 13 Permitted

This Site is not intended for use by people under eighteen (18) years of age. If you are under 18, please do not use this Site and do not send any information to us unless your parent or guardian are involved with your use of this Site. Persons under the age of 18 must not send any personal information to Recess under any circumstances, including but not limited to name, address or email address. 

### Who We Are

We are a provider of performance marketing technology used by marketers in industries including education, financial services, insurance, retail and lifestyle services. 

### Information We Collect

To provide advertisement that we believe may be useful to you, we collect information about your online activities, including your browsing history, information about which advertisements or web pages you viewed, clicked, or interacted with. You may be required to provide personally identifiable information to access or use parts of our Website. Personally identifiable information includes name, address, telephone number, email address, and any other data used or intended to be used to identify, contact or locate you. In addition, we may ask for certain sensitive consumer information which includes social security number to obtain additional information about you such as your credit score and/or your credit report to improve our matching service for you. If you do not provide the requested personally identifiable information, you may not be able to access or use the features of the Website. We may also ask for information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services; education level; educational interests; home owner status; income; debt level; current mortgage balance; mortgage rate and the like and other information that does not identify you. Cookies

When you visit our Site, we may collect certain information through the use of cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer. In addition to storing your preferences and other information, the cookies allow us to gather information about your interactions within our Site and/or on a given advertisement. We use both session cookies, which terminate when you close your browser, and persistent cookies, which remain on your computer until you manually delete them. You may decline our cookies if your web browser software permits. If you choose to accept cookies, you may choose to delete them later. You may access the "Help" option on your web browser's menu bar to instruct you on how to delete cookies.

Through the use of cookies, we collect information arising out of your use of our Site. When you visit our Site, we track certain non-personally identifiable information with respect to your activity on the Site. Your cookie information could consist of: the time of day an advertisement is displayed, an advertisement id that shows which advertisements you have clicked on, your IP address that shows your general geographic location and the referral id that shows the URL of the web page where you clicked on the ad, and/or other actions you conduct while on our Site. The cookies that we use will be set for 3 years.

We may use information we collect from cookies with any non-personally identifiable information that you provide to us as well as with your interaction with the Sites. The aforementioned information cannot, by itself, be used to gather any personally identifiable information about you. Third parties may also set cookies on or through the service to track Site usage and to track the overall effectiveness of our online advertising campaigns. We may combine cookie information with your personally identifiable information with your consent. 

### Log Files

When you visit our Website, we track IP addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp and number of clicks to analyze trends and administer the Site, track user's movement, and gather demographic information. We use your IP address at times to help identify you as you browse and to gather technical and demographic information on who uses the Site. 

### Web Beacons

We may use standard internet technology, called Web Beacons (also called clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs) that are tiny graphics with a unique identifier that are used to track online movements. Unlike cookies which are stored on the user's computer, a web beacon is embedded invisibly on a webpage (or email). Web beacons help us better manage content through the service by informing us and our third party partners what content and which campaigns are effective and to gauge the effectiveness of marketing campaigns by showing how many emails the recipients have opened or by sending/receiving an identification number when you travel to a site from an online advertisement. We do not tie web beacons to personally identifiable information without your opt in consent. 

### How We Use Your Information

In order to customize your experience, we show you advertisement(s) which we believe may be of interest to you based on the information we collect and our inferences from this information. The inferences may be based on several factors such as your cookie information, web beacon information, and any information that you provide or a combination of these with your opt in consent. We will not combine previously collected non-personally identifiable information with your personally identifiable information without your opt in consent. Similarly, we will not collect any sensitive consumer information such as social security numbers or financial account numbers without your opt in consent.

Based upon your affirmative opt in consent, as evidenced by your clicking on the applicable "submit" button, acknowledgement box, your registration on a Site, your submission of the requested information, including your personally identifiable information, we may use the information you provide to attempt to match you with providers of products and services and/or we may forward the information that you provided directly to our third party partners.

General: In general we may use information we collect about you to: 

  * Provide the products and services that you have requested;
  * Perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in our products, services, content, or the products, services, or content offered by third parties;
  * Communicate with you via email, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or third parties;
  * Develop and display content and advertisement tailored to your interests on our site and other sites;
  * Verify your eligibility to receive products and/or services;
  * Enforce our Terms of Service;
  * Manage our business; and
  * Perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

For example, we may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions, and accuracy; compare your information against publicly available files or commercially available data; and/or validate personal information to verify that the information you submitted has a high probability of being valid information. Use for Research: We may collect information about you and store it in connection with other online and/or offline information we may possess or obtain about you to create a general user profile.

### Email and Telephone Calls

From time to time, we or our business partners may contact you via e-mail advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, or other means to inform you of additional opportunities for other services and/or products that we believe may be of interest to you, even if you are listed on any federal, state or other applicable "Do Not Call" list. You are under no obligation to accept any service or product offered through these communications. We may maintain separate e-mail, mailing or phone lists for different purposes based on the information that you submitted and that we maintain. 

### Financial Information

To the extent that you provide your credit card information, we will use the information to verify your identity and/or for transmitting the information to the third party partners authorized by you for the purpose of completing your transaction. Such verification may be conducted through a third-party service provider and, in that case, we would share your specific credit card information with this third-party provider for verification purposes. Your credit card information will be encrypted during transmission. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may share with third-parties the fact that we have credit card information on file for specific users.

In the event we offer product and/or services where your credit card information is required to process your requested transaction, we will store your credit card information to facilitate your authorized transactions. Your credit card information is stored for a maximum of seven days. 

## Sharing your Information

### Third parties

WE MAY USE INFORMATION THAT WE HAVE COLLECTED FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE, INCLUDING SELLING OR TRANSFERRING SUCH INFORMATION AT ANY TIME TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE. For example, we may share your personal information with third party partners so that they can contact you and offer you products and/or services that we and they believe might be of interest to you. This may include, but is not limited to, e-mail advertising, telephone marketing, and direct mail marketing. By providing personal information when using the Sites, you are entering into a business relationship with Recess's third party partners and are requesting, and expressly consenting to, being contacted by our third party partners via telephone, fax, email, surface mail or any other means, at any of your contact numbers or addresses, even if you are listed on any federal, state or other applicable "Do Not Call" list, in order to provide the services set forth on the Site or for other purposes reasonably related to your expressed interest in the service and/or product request and the business of our third party partners, including marketing-related emails.

PLEASE NOTE: submission of YOUR telephone number(s) is YOUR authorization and request to be called at the telephone number(s) YOU provide.

We may disclose your personally identifiable information for the purpose of the transfer or sale of personally identifiable information pursuant to the sale of our business or assets. If we transfer ownership of the Site to another company, we will notify you by general notice on our Site. We may also transfer or share non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons visiting this Site. Service Providers

In order to provide the products or services you have requested, we may disclose the information we collect to companies that facilitate or provide elements of our service on our behalf, including without limitation, credit card processors, email management firms, and call center providers. We may also use external service providers to obtain your credit score and credit report.

### Other Purposes

We may also disclose your personally identifiable information when required by law, such as in response to a subpoena, court order, or other legal process, or to prevent imminent harm to any person or entity. We will fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal purposes. 

## How We Protect Your Privacy

### Security Measures

In order to protect both the personal information and the general information that we receive from you through our website, we have implemented various security measures. As an initial matter, any financial information (i.e. credit card information) transmitted to our servers via a secure server is encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") technology. SSL is a protocol that transmits your communications over the Internet in an encrypted form. The protocol ensures that the information is sent, unchanged, only to the server you intended to send it to.

Once your Financial Information reaches our server, it is protected by a firewall. In addition to encryption and firewall protections, our third party partners are required to operate in accordance with federal and state laws and regulations. If we learn that any of our third party partners is breaching our agreement, we will take corrective actions including, if necessary, terminate our relationship with such third party partner. 

### Risk of Interception

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online. For example, third parties may unlawfully intercept personal data or access our servers and obtain personal data. By using this site, you expressly acknowledge and agree that we do not guarantee the security of any data provided to or received by us through this site and that any personal information, or other data or information received from you through the site is provided to us at your own risk, which you expressly assume. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can mail us at the address indicated below in the Contact Us section. 

### Opting Out of Email Advertisement

If you wish to opt-out from receiving email offers containing advertisements and promotions relating to this Site, please click on this freebiegroceries.com to "opt-out".

If you choose to opt-out, your e-mail address will be added to the suppression files associated with this Site (e.g. Mortgage, Education etc.) within ten (10) business days of your request. Thereafter, you should not receive any further email offers containing advertisements and promotions from this Site. However you may still receive promotional communications from our third party partners with whom we have shared your information. To stop receiving further communications from these third party partners you will need to contact them directly in order to opt-out. Please note that after we process your request to opt-out from receiving additional email offers, advertisements and/or promotions from this Site, we will no longer make your information available to our third party partners relating to this Site. Effective Date and Notification of Changes to Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the Effective Date stated at the beginning of this Privacy Policy and will remain in effect except with respect to any of its provisions that are changed in the future, in which case the changes will become effective on the date they are posted on the Site. We will revise the "last updated" date found at the beginning of this Privacy Policy when we post changes to it. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. You should check this policy periodically as terms may change from time to time. Your continued use of the Site after we post any such changes constitutes your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments relating to our website or Privacy Policy, or if you would like to request information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties, please contact us by email, mail, or fax at:

Privacy@freebiegroceries.com

You may also send your questions or comments to our address:

Recess LLC  
Attention: Legal Department  
848 N. Rainbow Blvd. #1349, Las Vegas, NV 89107

### Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act

To the extent Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act, 15 U.S.C. 6802 (the "GLB Act") may apply to Recess's services (e.g. mortgage matching service), this Privacy Policy shall serve as your consumer "Privacy Notice" as defined under the GLB Act. Our services shall be deemed to conclude at the time you are matched with our participating service providers or when we notify you that we are not able to match you with any or of participating service providers. 

### Special Notification for California Residents

Individual customers who reside in California and have provided their personal information may request information regarding disclosures of this information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Such requests must be submitted through our Contact Us instructions. 

### Notification of Intellectual Property Rights Infringement

We are committed to uphold and respect intellectual property rights. If you are an intellectual property owner and believe that your rights have been infringed by materials on this webpage, please contact our Legal Department.

Recess LLC  
Attention: Legal Department  
848 N. Rainbow Blvd. #1349, Las Vegas, NV 89107

Please provide the following information in your correspondence to us: your name and contact information, identification of the copyrighted work claimed to be infringed, identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing, and sufficient information for us to locate the material. Please include with your correspondence, (i) a statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by you (copyright owner), your agent, or the law; (ii) a statement that the information you provided is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that you are authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
